fossies.org 2015-12-07

# Fossies - The Fresh Open Source Software Archive: Privacy Policy / Datenschutz

The "Fossies" Software Archive 

... Fresh Open Source Software mainly for Internet, Engineering and Science ... 

* * *

## Privacy Policy

While you access the "Fossies" archive, our web server temporarily records the following information for system security purposes: the IP address (or domain name) of the computer requesting access, the access date, the clients file request (file name and URL), the HTTP response code, the number of bytes transferred over the connection, and if applicable the website you are visiting from. 

We do not collect personal data such as your name, address, phone number or e-mail address unless you provide this information voluntarily, for example as part of an information request. 

The above mentioned personal data are only used for the purpose of technical website administration. We only disclose data to official agencies if required by law. 

## Datenschutz ("German language")

Bei Zugriffen auf das "Fossies" Archiv verzeichnet der Web-Server zum Zweck der Systemsicherheit temporär die IP-Adresse oder den Domain-Namen des anfragenden Rechners sowie das Zugriffsdatum, die Dateianfrage des Client (Dateiname und URL), den HTTP Antwort-Code und die Anzahl der im Rahmen der Verbindung transferierten Bytes, sowie gegebenenfalls die Website, von der aus Sie uns besuchen. 

Personenbezogene Daten wie Ihr Name, Anschrift, Telefonnummer oder Ihre E-Mail-Adresse werden nicht erfasst, es sei denn, diese Angaben werden von Ihnen freiwillig gemacht, z.B. im Rahmen einer Informationsanfrage. 

Die oben genannten personenbezogenen Daten werden nicht weitergegeben und nur zum Zwecke der technischen Administration des "Fossies"-Archivs genutzt. Gegenüber staatlichen Stellen werden Daten nur offen gelegt, wenn dies gesetzlich vorgeschrieben ist. 

* * *
